### Joshua Kolbusz

Address: 102 Stonebrook Drive, SC 29016, United States Phone Number: 224-704-8553

Email: joshuakolbusz@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Computer Science student who has worked in the manufacturing industry achieving 100+ edited videos and demoing new technology that would allow factory workers to check information on certain parts of the machine much quicker and safer.

### **Skills**

C++, C, Linux, Java, Python, Adobe Premiere/Photoshop, Microsoft Office, Communication Skills

### **Education**

# University of South Carolina | Columbia, SC Computer Science | 08/2023-Now

- Currently completing in a program to pursue a bachelor's degree in computer science
- Relevant courses: Data Structures and Algorithms (CSCE 350), Operating Systems (CSCE 311) Advanced Programming Techniques (CSCE 240)
- Member of Tau Sigma

#### **Midlands Technical College**

**Computer Science | 08/2020-08/2023** 

- Graduated summa cum laude 3.7+ GPA
- Achieved an Associate's Degree in Computer Science
- Relevant Courses: Unix Operating Systems (CPT 247), Intro to Computer Engineering I/II (ECE 211/212), Intro to Algorithmic Design I/II (EGR 281/283), Statistics for Engineers (EGR 209), Intro to Software Engineering (ECE 240)

## Work Experience

# Intertape Polymer Group – Nortech Packaging | Blythewood, SC Continuous Improvement Intern | 05/2022 – 01/2024

- Reviewed production schedules, engineering specifications, orders and related information to obtain knowledge of manufacturing methods, procedures and activities.
- Formulated sampling procedures and designs and developed forms and instructions for recording, evaluating and reporting quality and reliability data.
- Used Augmented Reality combined with a sight machine to check on the machines stability, virtually.

### Lowes Foods | Forest Acres, SC Meat Clerk/Cutter | 12/2020 – 12/2021

• Communicated with customers regarding orders, comments and complaints